"Listening to Dr. Cooper
(Penny:)has made me want to start
cutting myself again""
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Good evening,
Leonard, Howard, Raj,
(Leonard:)freeloader.
(Howard:)So, how'd the lecture go?
(Leonard:)In a word, triumphant.
(Leonard:)Really? Triumphant?
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes, you should have
seen those young people.
(Sheldon:)Thirsty for knowledge,
drinking in my wisdom.
(Sheldon:)I may have changed
a few lives today.
(Penny:)Oh, please let
me tell him.
(Leonard:)I don't know,
I kind of promised Howard.
(Sheldon:)Tell me what?
(Howard:)Actually, we should
all share the moment.
(Howard:)Raj, if you would.
(Sheldon:)Oh, tweets about my lecture.
(Sheldon:)Hmm...
(Sheldon:)That's rather unfair.
(Sheldon:)That's downright cruel.
(Sheldon:)Plus, insects
have six legs.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I'm not familiar
with the acronym "KMN""
(Leonard:)From the context, we think
it means "kill me now."
(Sheldon:)Well, I suppose everyone's
entitled to their own opinion.
(Sheldon:)I think I'll turn in.
(Sheldon:)I didn't want to teach
those poopy heads, anyway.
(Howard:)FYI, I think that's
what Darth Vader said
(Howard:)just before he started
building the Death Star.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪